Office of Price Administration
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Posters and Propaganda, undated, 1941-1943
  - Farmers, 1942 (Box 24:, Folder 1105)
  - “Figure It Out Yourself”, undated (Box 24:, Folder 1106)
  - 4-H, 1942 (Box 24:, Folder 1107)
  - Income Tax, 1942 (Box 24:, Folder 1108)
  - Materials in Spanish, 1942 (Box 24:, Folder 1109)
  - Minute Maids, 1942 (Box 24:, Folder 1110)
  - The Minute Men [5 issues], 1942 (Box 24:, Folder 1111)
  - “Minute Women at War Week”, 1942 (Box 24:, Folder 1112)
  - “Mrs. Brown Buys a War Bond”, 1941 (Box 24:, Folder 1113)
  - “Nation at War”, 1942 (Box 25:, Folder 1114)
  - Official Sales Agency Plaques, 1942 (Box 25:, Folder 1115)
  - “Organizational Chart: County or Local Women's Committees”, undated (Box 25:, Folder 1116)
  - “Paying for the War”, 1942 (Box 25:, Folder 1117)
  - “Plays for Victory”, 1942 (Box 25:, Folder 1118)
  - Postcard, undated (Box 25:, Folder 1119)
  - “A Program for Colleges”, 1942 (Box 25:, Folder 1120)
  - Schools at War, 1942-1943 (Box 25:, Folder 1121)
  - Second War Loan, 1943 (Box 25:, Folder 1122)
  - “Sharing America” Leaflets, undated (Box 25:, Folder 1123)
  - “Something New for Uncle Sam”, 1943 (Box 25:, Folder 1124)
  - “Songs for Service Club Meetings and Band Rallies”, undated (Box 25:, Folder 1125)
  - “The Story of America's Greatest War Loan”, 1943 (Box 25:, Folder 1126)
  - Third War Loan, 1943 (Box 25:, Folder 1127)
  - Union Members, undated (Box 25:, Folder 1128)
  - “What more can we do...”, undated (Box 25:, Folder 1129)
  - “Women's Drive for the 2nd War Loan”, undated (Box 25:, Folder 1130)
  - Women's Groups, undated (Box 25:, Folder 1131)
  - “Women's Handbook”, 1942 (Box 25:, Folder 1132)
  - Women's Playlets, undated (Box 25:, Folder 1133)
  - Zionist Organization of America, 1943 (Box 25:, Folder 1134)
  - War Bonds posters and materials, undated; [73 items] (Box 26:, Folder 1135)
  - War Bond Posters, undated; [46 items] (Box OS)